Bruno Santos

Junior Frontend Developer

I am a 27 years old frontend developer based in **Lisbon, Portugal**. From the moment I produced 'Hello World' in the console of my first application in 2014, I knew I was hooked into the world of programming.

Throughout the last 8 years, I have been developing applications and learning new technologies as a personal passion and hobby, and I now feel ready to step further into the world of programming and working within a team of inspiring minds.

www.brunosantos.dev github.com/humbruno +351 934 909 065



Professional Experience

Senior Treatment Coordinator @ Straight Teeth Direct

Jun 2020 - Present

- First point of contact for the platform's users
- Triage technical issues within the application to the respective Product Owners
- · Assist with training and integration of new team members

Customer Support Specialist @ Monese

Apr 2019 - May 2020

- Assist user gueries through various channels
- Implement customer support team's internal database of training material
- Attend daily standup meetings with the development team for upcoming platform updates and relay the information to the custom support team

Web Development Experience

Devfinder

www.devfinder.brunosantos.dev

Devfinder is a single-page application build with React.js - It works as a search engine for profiles on GitHub, using the platform's public API and the Axios library. The page also offers a light/dark theme toggle, built natively with SCSS and React's Context API

Solaris

www.planets.brunosantos.dev

Solaris is a webpage dedicated to our solar system, offering a navigation menu for each planet, as well as sub-categories for each item. The data is fetched from a local JSON file and redenred dynamically onto the page. It's built with React.js, SCSS and Vite.js

Skills

HTML

CSS / SCSS

JavaScript & TypeScript

React.js & Next.js

Bootstrap

Git

Tools

Visual Studio Code

Postman

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Languages

Portuguese (Native)

English (Fluent)

Education

2014-2015 - Web

Development Course

(Citeforma - Lisbon, Portugal)

2011-2014 - Maintenance of

Computer Hardware High

School Degree (Escola

Secundária de Alvide -

occaridaria ac / liviac

Cascais, Portugal)